I'm on an Alaskan cruise. I came here
with 13 of my family members. This ship
is huge. It's about the size of the
Eiffel Tower and holds around 5,000
people. There's so much to see and do.
And we'll be on the
Wow. And we'll be on the boat for 7
days. So, I'll take you along with me.
Let's go.
>> Are we the last [music] ones?
>> We're a minute early.
>> Oh, wow.
>> We got everyone.
>> Oh, it's [music] like an airport.
>> Take the health questionnaires.
>> Okay. [music]
>> Send your passport. Yeah,
>> we got our room keys and our boarding
pass.
[music]
>> We're boarding. This thing is huge.
Papa wheelie. Papa wheelie. Oh my gosh.
[music]
Coming in hot. [laughter]
Mind [music] blown. How is all of this
on a boat?
>> Hi. Can I get [music] the crab cake for
my appetizer? And I'll do the ribeye.
>> Would you like it to be
>> medium rare, please?
Salude. [laughter]
Here we are. Welcome to my crib. When
you first [music] come in, there's the
bathroom. Here's the toilet [music] and
shower.
Over here is the big king-size bed. It's
very comfortable. We've got a sofa
[music] here, a desk, but the best part
is
the balcony. [music]
They have some chairs. I sat and had my
coffee here this morning and enjoyed the
view. It's a little bit foggy today.
[music] I can't see any land.
We're going to deck seven. Have a bite
to eat. That don't open till 1:00. Then
we're going to go down to deck six for
love.
>> Yep.
>> All righty. Sounds good to me. They're
all booked. The go-karts still
>> double for the
>> They have go-karts on the ship, and we
wanted to try them out, but it's fully
booked, so we're going to grab a bite to
eat, have a drink, and do some trivia as
a family. Wish us luck. We're
competitive. We're going to try our best
to win this thing.
>> Thank you. Grandpa's napping cuz he was
at the casino all night. Three of
>> more.
I think it's time for a cocktail. Our
package has all drinks in food included,
so it's a little bit dangerous.
>> All righty. Espresso [music] martinis
saloon.
Damn, that's good. That is so good.
We're trying to play a game of celebrity
trivia, but it is packed. I guess this
is a popular game. Hopefully, we can
find a seat and participate.
>> My name is Andre. I'm part of the cruise
staff. We're always here doing and
hosting fun activities for you.
>> Is it a character?
>> Yes.
>> Is it an actor?
>> No.
>> Is it from a movie?
>> Yes.
Just lunch here.
>> No deal.
>> Yeah, you're right.
>> Deal.
>> No deal. No. No. No.
>> No deal. Two.
>> I'm hungry, so I'm going to the buffet.
They have so many options. It's almost
overwhelming. What do I get? Thank you.
Wow. I can feel the boat moving. It's
swaying. Or did [music] I have too many
cocktails?
My plate's a little messy, but I love
the variety of food they have here. I
think I'm [music] going to gain 50 lbs
on this trip.
Wow. For buffet food, the quality is
really good. It's fun eating at the
buffet cuz you can try so many different
kinds of food.
>> I'm tapping out. I hate wasting food,
but I think my eyes [music] were bigger
than my stomach. But of course, I always
have room for
Wow, that was a perfect swirl. [music]
If this whole YouTube thing doesn't work
out for me, I'm going to apply at an ice
cream shop.
My whole family's at the casino trying
to pay for this trip. Let's go. I just
dropped by my room and changed my
clothes because I was sweating. This
trip was really hard to pack for because
the weather is so unpredictable.
Sometimes it's freezing cold, there's
lots of rain, sometimes it's really hot.
You kind of just have to dress in layers
and hope for the best.
Did you win?
>> $73. Woo! Dinner's on you, huh? No.
>> [screaming]
>> All right.
>> 75. [laughter]
>> 40.
>> I just learned how to play Jack Black
[music] with my whole family. We didn't
win big, but we had fun. I think I mixed
up my words. Not Jack Black. That's an
actor. I learned blackjack.
Looks delicious. [music]
I got chicken breast with sweet potato
and corn on the cob. It looks so fancy
with the [music] little garnish on top.
Nice and juicy.
I'm with my beautiful mama who planned
this whole trip. She was the family's
travel agent for our Alaskan cruise. Was
it easy planning a trip for 14 people?
>> No, it [laughter] wasn't. It was fun
planning it. Just took a lot of going
over notes and making sure you didn't
miss anything.
>> How far in advance did you have to book
this vacation?
>> It was close to a year in advance. Like
11 months I really started planning it.
>> How much did the trip cost roughly?
>> Um it was roughly around 5,900 to 6,000
for each room. But the room was an
upgraded room that included a balcony
for every room, extra upgrades for
special meals, all of your drinks, your
internet, and your airfare. So, Wow.
>> You got a lot for the money.
>> Sounds like it. And you can buy
excursions on top of that, right? Is
that separate?
>> Yes, the excursions are separate that
you can either try to purchase on your
own outside of the ship or you can
purchase them through the ship. you get,
that's another one of the perks, a $50
credit towards the excursion. So, yeah,
there was a lot of perks.
>> That's good. Well, thanks for planning
the trip. I'm having a blast so far, and
I can't wait to make even more memories
together.
>> I'll be there with you.
>> All righty. [laughter]
>> Our goal is to get my grandma and
grandpa on the stage tonight. I'm going
to cheer for them so loud.
Gentlemen and welcome to today's room
for our [crying]
>> right here.
>> How long have you guys been married?
>> 68 68
married couple of us.
>> We have the longest married couple 68
years. We have to dust off the exior.
>> What's your name?
>> Jim and Shirley.
>> Jim and Shirley. Oh, red. Wow. And what
size?
>> I think it's 34, right? A little bit of
a
muscle. IT'S A MATCH. KISS. KISS. KISS.
And what would you make smaller?
>> Probably my belly.
>> Yes.
[cheering]
>> You did good. You did good. That was
fine.
>> Yeah. We're going up. Okay.
>> All right. Good night. See you in the
morning. Good night.
It's 5:30 a.m. and I'm up and ready to
go to the gym. Let's go.
>> Good morning. [laughter]
This is my stepsister Dana and she's the
gym rat of the family. [laughter]
>> What time do you wake up to go to the
gym? Usually,
>> um, usually I get up at 4:40 a.m. Damn,
that's commitment. You can tell she's
got a rocking bod. So, [laughter]
>> well, thank you. She's going to whip us
into shape today. Woohoo. [laughter]
>> That's right. Damn, girl. Your muscles
are popping. [laughter]
>> Okay. No. Done. I'm going to be sore
tomorrow.
[music]
Running out of steam here. Yeah,
>> I know.
>> It's hard.
>> I'm done. KO got to finish up with the
selfie.
Hello.
I think that should do it. Thank you.
>> We're being fancy this morning. Room
service is kind of included in your
package. You can order all the food you
want, but you do have to pay a service
fee. So, for breakfast, we paid $5, but
it's a little bit more expensive for
lunch, dinner, and late night. I wanted
to eat it on the balcony, but it's super
rainy, so I don't think that's going to
happen today. Let's unpack [music] this.
If you want to order room service, all
you have to do is fill out a form and
[music] hang it on your door before 4:00
a.m. So, I did that last night. Okay.
Some toast. A little crispy, slightly
[music] burnt, but that's okay. This is
a breakfast bento. We have [music] a few
pastries, fresh fruit, hot coffee,
French toast, and two different kinds
[music] of omelets. I think we have a
good variety here. Let's dig in. I moved
because [music] I didn't want to get
crumbs on the bed. I'm buttering the
toast.
M. It's good, [music] but probably the
buffet omelets are better because
they're made fresh to order. This is
kind [music] of nice if you want to have
breakfast on your balcony. We were just
unlucky today.
M the French toast is the bomb. So good.
I like it [music] with extra maple syrup
drizzled on top. I ordered two coffees
thinking [music] they were going to
bring me two cups of coffee and they
brought me two cars full of coffee. Too
much caffeine. [music]
>> [snorts]
>> Today is our first [music] day off the
boat. We're in Sika, Alaska.
Right now, we're waiting in line to get
on the shuttle bus. It'll take us
downtown. Woohoo! We're on land. We made
it to Alaska finally.
for you
anytime you want. They give you
if you made reservations, um I wouldn't
worry about it and something happens
where you got to get back, you know, at
your
>> pro tip, if you go on a cruise, bring
your own snacks. There's no convenience
store on board. Luckily, my family comes
prepared.
My mom and my grandma hooked me up. And
now I'm going to go on the balcony
because we're supposed to sail past some
glaciers. Let's check it out.
[laughter]
Thanks, Mom and Grandma.
>> Hi, Mom.
>> Whoa.
>> My family's rooms are all in a row, so
we peek over the balcony and talk to
each other. Graham, wave. Hi.
>> Hi there.
>> Be Uncle Greg.
>> [laughter]
>> The scenery is [music] so beautiful.
Look at how blue this water is. And
there's some icebergs floating out
there, too. I got my binoculars [music]
in case I want a closer look.
Ooh, wow. Look at all of those icebergs
[music]
out there.
There's the glacier straight ahead.
You're a baby.
>> I'm a baby. Yeah. Everyone knows
granddaughters are the favorite.
>> It's true. It's true. Fact.
>> I'm the favorite grandson-in-law.
[laughter]
>> I'm at Tepanyaki with my whole family.
It's basically dinner and a performance.
They grill the food right at your table,
so it's very fresh and delicious.
>> How are you,
>> my size, baby?
>> All right,
>> gets the spot.
>> We'll make it. [music and singing]
Oh,
>> thank you so much.
>> Thank you.
>> This is the third person in our family.
The camera always. [laughter]
It's day five of our cruise. We were off
the boat all morning whale watching.
[music] It was amazing. I'm on a mission
now to play mini golf. It's a bit chilly
and windy today. What's this? I think
this is the adults only zone. It looks
like the best seat in the house. They've
got a hot tub right at the back of the
ship. I want to check that out one day.
My grandma's coming up here to play with
us, and she's the best golfer I know.
So, she's probably going to kick my
butt. All right, go for it.
I didn't hit mine hard enough.
[laughter]
>> I think so, too.
>> We all did the same. [laughter]
>> Woo! There we go.
Nice, Grim.
All right.
[screaming]
Pull in one.
>> Two.
Graham, our winner.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Our putt putt champ. [laughter]
>> I won.
>> I got lucky on that one. I put someone
else's ball in my hand.
>> She's being humble.
>> I know. It's freezing today.
>> There they are. [screaming]
>> Careful. Let's go.
>> Baby goat carts.
>> [laughter]
>> That looks more fun than these go-karts.
>> Yeah.
>> Hello.
>> You excited for the show?
>> Heck yeah. This is music from my genre.
>> What decades is this from?
>> Um 70s, 80s. They're playing my sticks.
>> Are you going to sing along?
>> Heck yeah.
[cheering]
>> [singing]
[music]
>> to me.
Oh, won't you please take me home?
[singing]
every time.
[music]
[singing]
>> Did you like it?
>> I loved it. Woo! [screaming]
She was rocking out.
>> Rock on.
This morning we spent some time in
Ketchacan. It was our last morning
getting off the ship. Now I'm hanging
out with my family in the observation
lounge. I'm going to play some games
with my family. When you're when it's
your turn, you take a delivery card and
a joke card. You got to tell the joke
how the delivery card tells you. If you
get him to laugh, you get the point. If
you don't get him to laugh,
>> you lose.
>> No point.
>> Okay. All right. Here we go. Ready?
Remember the rules.
>> Don't ever try to
laugh and laugh.
[laughter]
>> I don't know. in the bathroom.
>> Wow,
>> there's so many.
>> Probably cuz it's warm today.
>> Yep, it's hot today. It's nice and
sunny. Finally.
I just watched the most beautiful sunset
from my balcony. Tonight is our last
family dinner on the cruise. We're going
out for Italian food. I dressed up a
little bit for the occasion. Fit check.
>> All right, I'm going to say something
short, sweet
all this. It's been a sacrifice for
everybody
and it's been yours.
Cheers everyone.
>> Let me [singing] call you sweetheart.
>> I'm in love
with you. [cheering]
[applause]
>> Uncle John Chris, you stopping by the
club?
>> 10:00. It's a glow party. Floor six.
Dana's coming down.
>> Are you going dancing tonight?
>> I'm just going with her.
>> Oh, come on. He's going to be tearing it
up on the dance floor. [laughter]
>> I want to sing karaoke. We're hitting
the club.
>> Hey. Hey. [music]
>> [music]
[cheering]
[music]
>> Good morning.
>> I kind of want a fresh omelette this
morning.
Thank you so much. It's our last day on
the ship, so I'm determined to swim, but
it's a little cold out right now, so
this is my swim fit. It's kind of weird.
I have on my swimsuit with jeans and
Uggs. Maybe this will help warm me up.
[laughter] You showed off before.
>> Yeah. Come on. Yeah.
>> What?
>> The Mr. Sexy Legs.
>> Oh, yeah. You got nice legs. [laughter]
>> It would make grandma and grandpa's trip
much better.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
[screaming]
Mr. Sexy Legs.
>> Go them up though.
>> This is John.
>> My name is Hong. I'm from South Korea.
The reason why I'm buying length sex is
that my 14 family member even said I got
this.
[cheering]
[screaming]
>> [cheering]
>> He's going to be tearing it up on the
dance floor. [cheering]
[cheering]
[screaming]
>> They just had a Mr. Sexy Legs
competition and guess who the winner
was? the cameraman.
[laughter]
He did a great job. He was such a great
sport. My family kind of signed him up
without his consent, but he did amazing.
And I had a lady come up to me and say,
"Well done." I think she's saying that
the cameraman is good-looking, very
handsome. I'm so proud.
There's two water slides on this boat.
And usually I'd be all over it, but I'm
too much of a chicken today because it's
so cold out.
Wow. This slide is literally hanging off
the side of the boat. That's pretty
intense.
>> Someone's coming right there.
>> That's crazy. That's nuts. We got our
drinks and we're at the back of the boat
in the adult only zone. It's cold
outside, but it's nice and toasty in the
hot tubs. So, I think I'm going to be
here for a little while today. It's very
quiet and peaceful back here.
>> Peaceful.
>> We're going to enjoy the last day.
Cheers.
I'm here with my grandma and grandpa.
They're the whole reason why we're here
on this trip. So, I'm going to ask them
some questions. Why did we come to
Alaska?
>> Well, it was in my bucket list and I
finally emptied the bucket. I I was able
to finance the kids along or us and here
we are. It's a trip we've talked about
for many, many years and never did
because there was always something else
to spend money on. And we've reached a
point in our life that we wanted to do
something special. And last year,
grandpa had a accident and broke his
femur bone. And our three children were
there for us every step of the way. It's
a thank you to them.
>> It's something that you will never
forget in your whole life. and uh you
can bring back memories and through your
videos and everything else. And
>> absolutely. Speaking of memories, I know
it's hard to choose, but so far on the
trip, what's one of your favorite
memories?
>> I think what it is is seeing [snorts]
everybody enjoying themselves and uh
being together as a family, it made it
that much more special for us and
hopefully for you guys, too.
>> I mean, FaceTime is wonderful. However,
being right there together is wonderful,
too. It's
>> no can't beat it.
>> And grandma and grandpa won the old age
contest for years marriage, which was 68
years marriage. And Hong, he won a prize
today for the most beautiful legs.
[laughter]
>> What's next on the bucket list? Maybe
coming to South Korea to see one of my
great grandchildren. [laughter]
How about that, girl?
>> Is that a hint hint nudge nudge?
[laughter]
>> All right. If it gets you to South
Korea, we'll start working on that.
[laughter]
>> How about you, Grim?
>> You know, I don't really have a bucket
list at this stage of the game in our
lives. We just want to stay as healthy
as possible and we just want to enjoy
our life and and we are we have a good
life. Well, I just want to say thank you
to you both. We're so happy that we
could make it and we've [music] had so
much fun with you guys. You guys are
really a big inspiration for me and for
Hung. I love you.
>> I love you.
>> Oh, my head's ruined in the moment.
>> Thank you for watching and we'll see you
next time. Bye.
>> We're in Alaska.
>> Oh, he's so close. Oh my gosh. Yay.
s of strength.
[laughter]
>> Hallelujah.